degoo.com 2003-06-27

# d e g o o . c o m - Get paid to see advertisements

|   

### Privacy Statement for degoo.com

Degoo Media has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: degoo.com.

We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their interests, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to show the user promotional material from some of our partners. Degoo will not share, sell, trade, or give away personally identifiable information to third parties without members' explicit permission. If the user does not want to receive any more promotions he or she may cancel their account at any time, read more about cancelling your account in "Choice/Opt-Out" section below. 

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. 

### Promotional Offers

Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Degoo customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give third party marketers your name and address. 

### Business Transfers

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that Degoo Media AB or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets. 

### Security

We take the responsibility of protecting the integrity of our Members information seriously and use industry standard procedures and processes to safeguard the confidentiality of our Members identifiable personal information and to track abuse of our network and our data. However, the internet is not a 100% secure medium and we may not have control over submitted information during all phases of our relay between a Member and us. 

### Children's Guidelines

No one under the age of 18, except for Swedish members where the age-limit is 16, is allowed to join, advertising can therefore never be targeted to children. 

### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

We give users the option for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

Visit the following URL: **http://degoo.com/scipts/members/deleteform.php** if you wish to cancel your account 

### Correct/Update

We give users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

 Visit the following URL: **http://degoo.com/scipts/members/updateform.php** if you wish to update your information

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Carl Hasselskog  
Degoo Media AB  
Briger Jarlsgatan 37  
111 45 Stockholm  
Sweden
